Hello Hello friends welcome back to another
new with Sand Art in this video we will talk
if you had joined the ICICI edit partner
program if you
got your user ID password then after that
how to use the debit, your
ICICI debit card has a chunky link,
how to find that link, then
how to repair the Anushree link only,
friends a few days ago I was talking about
how to restore the puja in case the parents are scheduled, good friends today
in this video I will tell you completely how to
log in to the edit pandu song, how to
create your referral link, in this
way after people notice whatever is
recorded in your device, then it is
very important otherwise by
earthquake revise and ask do not miss even a second
and this video will not be too long
friends before going ahead in the video let me
tell you one thing that there is a
new puja on the nutrition knowledge channel,
right now subscribe to the subscribe
button on the shop face,
click on it and the gum next to it
Click on it and select the poor
because on this channel you can see the entire
₹10 note whose direction you
can see first of all, then you can go to Sadho
or there is also a very old video which was done
in the rally with guava, after seeing which
you will be able to solve many problems,
so every online earning has a big
double password online, this app dos you
can also watch my channel yes date of birth is Vidya short fiction, you will also get
Rustagi business live, so
friends let's start today's video,
you friends, interesting channel ismart hua
lite friend 1919 subscribe, so
I have to
login to it, friends, I got my Android
dip, first of all friends, to know this point, first of all you have to
click on it on the side, after that
subscribe subscribe, so you can subscribe so that
friends first of all
subscribe subscribe download from and to
and click on subscribe to my channel,
Facebook Pinterest injection digital wrong has to be improved,
please I have presented friends,
you can see the option of account opening here
It has come, see, you
can give a missed call from a number four wheel drive, you have
not opened an online account, then after that
you can subscribe to someone, paste this
virus 98100, then do
not forget to share it and if you want to subscribe then the
team members will start,
how do I check the messages, let me tell you, this
ICC debit in support is very less, it is
very deluxe, there are so many
options, it is going to be confusing for you,
but there are many shortcomings in this side, I would
recommend you and I will be, you should
join the IAS partner program, if you do not do this then
if you have the CR button then which better
program than this, I will also
send you a reminder and then that bed has been prepared,
sorry link share mutual fund of
fund, if you have joined then you will have to submit its report, so
see how, so
friends, you have to come to this fast option dashboard from that shampoo,
after coming to a sad board, you can see here, a very
Swastika meter will start on your time
123456789 The time will start but
friends here I will tell you this bile of your
face,
this quarter inch for boy where it is written
first number chilli and mrs pay target
phone number gift number the meter in the MCA
target will work in this direction, whatever happens
in your mind will start working on it,
so see here my entire
accounts till now should remain poor can
other obscenity results in these eggs
what is the problem in this like on August
uttam pandey join in the past whichever
friend give your mobile institute mobile
number email in this way so that he deletes the
shopping work it does not matter by
asking your details your desume hu comes i.e.
what is his name mobile number email
id card images are asked, there is a
problem in reading from that no one will
see any details of active members untill after
its north-east corner is fitted until
its eyes
media swells impartially then there will be
zero in your dashboard second
clear ka two and guilty Twenty20 series
Present this ad, this customer, his account has been opened,
so that means he had
not subscribed yet, he had not subscribed yet,
hence one or two members will subscribe,
dial the mobile number,
sleeping had not happened, you will get the details on that,
where will you be appointed in this show, it will
not be stuck, only in NCA, whatever this is also
considered, if you get up and take it, then you will remember,
in this I was crushed
for a membrane, subscribe, subscribe,
subscribe to this channel,
coat 50 stock oil, then your f-35 will be there, only then
you will get the distorted face, oh
daughter-in-law, whichever member is active, will specialize in its details, so
this option 323 sculpture has to be done,
prepare the tap, then see, it is
active in two pairs, then his name is Vishal Kumar,
subscribe,
from the mobile number I have to call him, subscribe to his mobile
number, email ID of
that customer, the mobile number in Gmail
ID will start, but the customer who was
in practice till now, Hussain quantity,
Khanduri, then his details will be given to
you in this loop fast food number continuously
friends, this  I had told you this, still
if you yourself Sunday fennel and me the mean
time broom comment then friends, this
year's syllabus is something special, I just
felt that you should tell its result, dare you are
interested in ugly partner photo, if
you want then only increase tiffin top,
former director of Angel Broking, then
its enjoyment is also more than ICI and
his de is very innocent filmy, he was
appointed MLA a decade ago, your
day will come in August,
by subscribing to the customer, when the power of the matter is there, do
not forget to subscribe to this channel in the dark, thank you